prince5 = [
{"question":"既","Answer":"jì"},
{"question":"耀眼","Answer":"yàoyǎn"},
{"question":"麵包","Answer":"miàn bāo"},
{"question":"附近","Answer":"fùjìn"},
{"question":"偶爾","Answer":"ǒuěr"},
{"question":"零星","Answer":"língxīng"},
{"question":"麵包屑","Answer":"miàn bāoxiè"},
{"question":"啄食","Answer":"zhuóshí"},
{"question":"伸展","Answer":"shēnzhǎn"},
{"question":"藉此","Answer":"jiècǐ"},
{"question":"差不多","Answer":"chàbuduō"},
{"question":"氣息","Answer":"qìxī"},
{"question":"肩膀","Answer":"jiānbǎng"},
{"question":"親吻","Answer":"qīnwěn"},
{"question":"傳","Answer":"chuán"},
{"question":"鏗鏘","Answer":"kēngqiāng"},
{"question":"聲響","Answer":"shēngxiǎng"},
{"question":"爆裂","Answer":"bàoliè"},
{"question":"交叉路口","Answer":"jiāochālùkǒu"},
{"question":"盯着","Answer":"dīng zhe"},
{"question":"驚懼","Answer":"jīngjù"},
{"question":"雕像","Answer":"diāoxiàng"},
{"question":"嚷着","Answer":"rǎng zhe"},
{"question":"帶","Answer":"dài"},
{"question":"獨具慧眼","Answer":"dújù huìyǎn"},
{"question":"盡情","Answer":"jìnqíng"},
{"question":"結果","Answer":"jiéguǒ"},
{"question":"付出","Answer":"fùchū"},
{"question":"一副","Answer":"yīfù"},
{"question":"心腸","Answer":"xīncháng"},
{"question":"而得","Answer":"ér dé"},
{"question":"圍觀","Answer":"wéiguān"},
{"question":"熔爐","Answer":"rónglú"},
{"question":"熔化","Answer":"rónghuà"},
{"question":"禁止","Answer":"jìnzhǐ"},
{"question":"立","Answer":"lì"},
{"question":"初","Answer":"chū"},
{"question":"竟","Answer":"jìng"},
{"question":"簇擁","Answer":"cùyōng"},
{"question":"秋涼","Answer":"qiūliáng"},
{"question":"際","Answer":"jì"},
{"question":"巷","Answer":"xiàng"},
{"question":"願","Answer":"yuàn"},
{"question":"市議員","Answer":"shìyìyuán"},
{"question":"漂亮","Answer":"piàoliang"},
{"question":"廣場","Answer":"guǎngchǎng"},
{"question":"正中央","Answer":"zhèng zhōngyāng"},
{"question":"附和","Answer":"fùhè"},
{"question":"心臟","Answer":"xīnzàng"},
{"question":"苦惱","Answer":"kǔnǎo"},
{"question":"幸福","Answer":"xìngfú"}
]